[Music]
meeeee
fore
[Music]
foree
the one on the left is Rosie Red she's
one of my favorites because she's so
very cute and that one on the right is
Charlotte Starlite I don't like her very
much because of her weird clown cap so I
make her live in the closet what about
that one by the window in the Potted
soil that's lender the Thunder baby
Sonic and manic accidentally left her
outside in the rain using her as a
soccer ball and she was struck by
lightning why Sonia I must say you do
have a fine assortment of dolls and I
see you are still hanging on to miss
pretty bottom I'm surprised you haven't
thrown her out by now after you know the
event it's okay mama she can't go
anywhere because I locked her down with
a ball and chain she is my Shackled
prisoner oh then why is the key there
next to her
feet haha Miss pretty Bottom now how in
the world did you get that you know
you're not allowed to touch things thei
was in the clock it I don't know how she
got it I believe you sweet pee now let's
go find your party Crown so we can go to
Chuy
cheese
yeah
[Applause]
woo mother we require more refreshment
and make with the tokens already [__]
we're ready to game what the did you
just snap at me I didn't have to buy you
$468 worth of pepperoni pizza you know
what I said I wanted three meat not
extra pepperoni this is worse than when
you mistook cinnamon raisin bread for
cinnamon toast crunch sister give me a
party cup I must pee away my sorrows
before going to town on that pizza the
bathroom is right over there literally
nobody at the stable asked four
directions you cotton candy looking
ass dumbass
[Music]
[__] yo yo yo Knuckles the cool
up getting her in the house who's ready
to party I brought a bag of boiled eggs
what up nuck come join the fun hey at
there they didn't turn me away this time
you can't go
home hey keep an eye on that kid now
will you pretty sure he's prone to
stealing from us though we haven't found
any legal proof for conviction yet what
Knuckles has never stolen anything from
us besides a can of ravioli a pool
noodle Uncle Chuck's mustache comb and
my Nintendo switch sup you guys are
going to love the present I got you it
goes so [__] well with the pool in
your backyard Knuckles is my special
little guy even though it drives him
crazy when I call him that why do you
hate him mama and Mindy too you hate all
two of my friends it's nothing personal
baby cakes it's just well he's a
kidner but but I brought eggs and I hear
our kidas tend to be very unclean CU
they dig in the ground a lot wrong I
smell good since I wear Apollo wax body
spray y Mama isn't it a mother's job to
prioritize her children's happiness no I
will not stand for my kids hanging out
with a dirty Digger you're wrong about
him he's not just some dumb uneducated
Digger he's one of the good ones son you
don't defy me I'd rather not beat you on
your birthday hey you can't boss us
around on our birthday you old heg
Knuckles is my best bud he goes where I
go perfect I don't like you either so
take him and leave so Sonia can go and
date a wholesome Hedgehog boy I remember
when I was banned on an online Forum
once because I called someone a digger
hey me too it's a small world it was
probably because you said it with a hard
R I was using it in an educational sense
it's not like I go online and just call
people diggers happens to the best of us
I'm sure they're just trying to keep the
forums safe y gunky poops you can't
Sayer and be surprised if you get Auto
band context or not there are probably
systems in place to stop that well
they're doing a piss poor job of it
because their Defiance only makes me
want to say it war God I hate diggers me
too I agree exactly most
definitely are we still talking about a
kidness oh [__] you fetched me a drink
how gracious of your fat
ass honest to God my lover I just
emptied my balls into this pretty cup I
suppose it would be better than pooping
in it w
hot damn baby now that some damn good
lemonade you nasty [__] you're just
asking for trouble with that little Ploy
I might have to charge you by the way I
got you this present [__] open it up
birthday boy before I have my way with
your birthday
at Holy Moly front R SE tickets to the
newus walk concert but Bart leby how did
you know you have [__] taste in music
from the look on your face I guess I did
good what can I say birthday K cat
Chuck-E-Cheese with my friends this has
already been the best birthday party of
my whole life what sort of band calls
themselves bisw they call themselves
that because they piss all over the
place while playing their music the only
band that's ever been able to upstage
them was
poop hey but
hole unless I am mistaken we've been in
chuckecheese for 17 minutes and I still
don't have a bundle of t
just as away in my panties where's the
good [__] you promised us who hired the
birthday clown with the balloon lips he
smells like expired milk and
peanuts that's not a clown mama that's
manx hooker
[Music]
girlfriend so these three are the
Destroyers of the royal Hedgehog
bloodline a dirty hole an Aida and a
star studded trillionaire [__] God
somebody please just kill
me with monsters was ready
to for well things seem to be going well
I think I'll go swap granola bar recipes
with other
moms one talk each you think this is
funny [__] quite dle shuck you must
have the biggest pair of balls on Earth
how dare you hold on out on us it's our
birthday you old fart you can't just ho
the tokens all for
yourself stop it let go of my present
you think you
present oh my God Son quick call the
cops winner winner winner winner look
[__] Sonic's uncle is opening the
present what did he get
gross me this PA oh boy I love peas
they're like little green candies Sonia
please accept this with my full
gratitude this allinone sweet box
includes four dozen Belgian chocolates
covered in decadently sweet 71% pure
cocoa dusting that will provide what is
a truly Out of This World experience and
know that our running into each other
here is purely coincidential get the
[__] out of here you weren't on the
birthday
list roseb te one of the many pleasures
of being a
wealthy
uh kid daddy say she to play unless you
want a Spanky from Daddy I'm sorry but
you are going to have to wait your turn
I just put a token
in
because no more how about you piss off
before I suck you your balls and eat out
your ass you can't make me
move dude just chill out like a popsicle
in Alaska my guy it's only a
game is
[Music]
s
and then I said powdered sugar I thought
you meant granulated sugar ha haa ha haa
then what happened well he punched me in
the but it was funny up until that point
mommy H Sonic dear why are you weeping
have you pooped yourself again I'm
telling you the DI opposite Wallgreens
will hold a lot of your [__] no Mommy I
didn't well I did but that's not what
this is about it's Uncle Chuck Mama He's
hoarding all of the tokens from us and
our bodies and now our friends are
threatening to go home because our
birthday party sucks we're trying to
have fun Mama truly but it's just so
hard because of your defiant brother he
what no one gets away disrespecting my
babies
oh what have we here you sure seem to be
enjoying
yourself perfect te daddy is ruing
not out of the seat game's over no yes
no yes
[Music]
no okay I think I'm starting to see the
full picture you're trying to live
vicariously through my own [__] kids
because your own life sucks balls and i'
i' never through US birthday parties yes
nothing
but you know when Sonic told me you were
acting like a fat old Goblin hoarding
game tokens I thought there had to be
some kind of mistake
no
who the hell was
that I don't believe this you actually
don't see the problem with how we
behaving do you no and you think think
you're going to get away with this yep
you know bro sometimes I think you
forget that kids are actually people
that are going to remember these
things get but M Aunt we promised them a
birthday party and you crushed it
beneath your heel you are a cold
manipulative old man and I assure you we
will never forget
this where Domingo you think you going
aren you going to stay and watch me for
the first in
I'm going to celebrate with my kids have
fun watching my asses I walk away don't
youat loser loser
loser loser loser loser loser
[Music]
loser
sore street at the
corner of
Riverside we were young and we were
Lon you asked me for a ride where did we
drive that
day I don't
remember no matter better
any way for the place cuz the smile on
your
face cast a Golden Glow and made my soul
surrender hot damn ble be you got Sonic
good in that game of air hockey how are
you so good cuz I'm [__] M bab
[__] hey Knuckles can you go tell my
girlfriend to stop man at horse will do
what horse will do no I mean she's
scraping her knife and fork on her salad
plate it's her way of telling me we need
to
talk but I don't care enough to go over
there hey [__] if there is something
you want to say then spit it out oh it's
nothing okay actually there is something
I know hurry up every everyone else is
having pizza while I'm am left here
alone to eat salad I brought from home
okay well considering I'm on a diet you
would think that my friends would have
accommodated my needs without relying on
me to bring my own healthy meal
alternative bye it's their birthday well
shame on you for shame this is the last
time I come to a party where I wasn't
even
invited
manic I want to have a word with you
he's in the
bathroom manic I want to have a word
with you what I'm leaving okay as my
boyfriend okay I wasn't
done as my boyfriend I don't think it's
right for you to have fun on your
birthday
okay are we done or are you going to let
me finish [__] I really don't [__]
care to be honest just say what you want
and
go I don't think it's right for you to
have fun on your birthday without
accommodating my
needs that's fine you weren't invited
anyway the free birthday lap dance you
gave me already made me look like a
badass to the
12-year-olds so your usefulness has come
to an end you may
go Mindy why are you back so soon did
all of the makeup on your face call a
chemical reaction so bad that they had
to close down the Chuck-E-Cheese
building to avoid kids passing out from
the toxins no Daddy you remember how I
told you I was invited to the Hedgehog
triplets birthday party not really well
I lied oh baby girl I keep telling you
this will happen until you can find some
real friends who will treat you like a
person and night mounds of silicone
implants trapped inside massive
counterfeit bits bought on the streets
and babwe anyway change of topic my G
Bros dropped off some power oats how
would you like to join me in making some
no Bak cookies haha old Addie you know
with all of my plastic surgery sessions
that eating anything that isn't organic
would kill me oh yes I forgot the last
plastic surgeon said your life
expectancy is drastically low since
you're more silicone than organic being
so you're most likely going to die
before turning 21 thanks for reminding
me sugar BN you're welcome daddy now
let's make those cookies I can't eat
them but at least I can smell
them you have fun with those tokens baby
I'm going to the bathroom because I have
diarrhea and your father won't [__] my
ass if I have Po in
there hey Sonic do you see what I see a
sweet little girl I see prey Sonia we
can't just go over there and steal a
little girl's tokens
why not because that would be evil but
aren't good and evil simply mental
constructs of the men who hold the power
mom really needs to stop reading uhp
Lovecraft but you're right let's go make
Bank winner winner
winner
winner winner
winner you know everybody we don't need
to cause a Ruckus over some silly little
tokens why back in the good old days
before the internet people didn't need
arcade games to have fun they played
real games real games like
[Music]
what
he he musical chairs is so fun and silly
too but just wait until the Music Stops
and we have to race for the chat that's
when the real fun
begins hey blue guy I saw you kissing
that blonde guy on the loops today but
you're both boys like me why did you do
that why it's because we are G and I
love
him what does game mean it means they
chase down little boys in Alleyways and
rape them no it doesn't stop spreading
lies about us ex cheese never lies to
kids so you're rapist if Chucky Cheese
says you're rapists then that's what you
are you're [__] up you deserve to be
handcuffed and tied on a train track to
be run over you little [__] face you
better Hur this song doesn't end soon
because when it does I'm coming over
there and slushing those godamn ties and
then I'm going to make you hurt like a
but cheek on a stick
are you better ride off godamn [__]
I'm coming to your
ass I
win hola
everybody oh Uncle what the [__] are you
doing here shouldn't you be off playing
games somewhere with all of the those
tokens you're giving them to us but
why St and faceing so want
for and if your KS me oh how could we
ever stay mad at you uncle you're are
cool Uncle Chuck you know how to make
cool pancake art my great-grandfather
does that too like when he puts two
pancakes next to each other with the
pile of chle chips in the middle so it
looks like a big poopy
[Music]
butt he
you yeah
who was that Uncle
Chuck I think it's
for your grandfather the grandfather of
Sonic T Kevin
[Music]
T Kevin the Hedgehog you have a
visitor
can't get story before it
closes
lemons from
Lon
Nots want to
make pick up
the
and what looking
things words
yourid the name is manic Manic the
Hedgehog I'm the coolest Hedgehog in
[Music]
town excuse me we're triplets so if you
say that you're talking about all of
[Music]
us what's
your I'm Sonic
Sonic I named him Sonic because Sonic
was a fast
baby what's your
name I'm Sonia I like unicorn drawings
Andre
that's a stupid it's Sonic
with that's
[Music]
fuing damn [__] there's a [__] ton of
black people here well they don't call
Al a prison for
nothing
[Music]
was
for Uncle Chuck why did you have to show
him to us he was mean and scary
I'm
sorry it was important for that monsters
in whatever hey Sonic look look who it
is yo it's the little [__] from
Chuck-E-Cheese that we beat up and
behind her are two members of the band
piss walk I knew I recognized her from
somewhere who would have thought that we
beat the piss out of the lead singer of
pisw
oh did I fail to mention that not only
did I buy you ticket Beach but they were
for a special inperson concert so they
followed us all the way to alcatra
prison just for you you'll really play
for me even after I beat you up I'm
going to ignore that this one goes out
to you barnab be's [__] there isn't
anywhere at all we would rather be than
in front of HRA prison today blasting
some of our Rock in Tunes with our balls
hanging out while we [__] pee
two two
[Music]
three
for
[Music]
for Uncle Chuck watch out they're about
to piss and you're standing in the
Splash
[Music]
Zone awesome D that was a lot of F I
wouldn't expect anything less from Good
Old fish BX
[Music]
call
Chi ch
[Music]
ch
forea
[Music]
ch